Digital Collections and Archives Records UA069
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Digital objects, 1662 -- 2015; 2000 -- 2004; UA069.005; 542 Digital Object(s)
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1916, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00125; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Basketball (Women's); Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1917, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00126; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Tennis (Women's); Track (Women's); Baseball; Football; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1918, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00127; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Track; Tennis; Baseball; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1919, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00128; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Wrestling; Track; Tennis; Baseball; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1920, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00129; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Basketball; Baseball; Track; Wrestling; Tennis; Football; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1921, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00130; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Field Hockey; Football; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1922, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00131; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Baseball; Basketball (Men's); Basketball (Women's); Tennis (Women's); Tennis (Men's); Track (Men's); Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1923, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00132; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Tennis; Track and Field; Baseball; Football; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1924, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00133; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Basketball (Men's); Basketball (Women's); Football; Tennis (Men's); Track (Men's); Wrestling; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1925, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00134; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Baseball; Basketball (Men's); Cross Country (Men's); Football; Tennis (Men's); Track and Field; Wrestling; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1926, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00135; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Baseball; Basketball (Men's); Basketball (Women's); Field Hockey; Cross Country (Men's); Football; Track (Men's); Wrestling; Tennis (Men's); Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1927, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00136; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Baseball (Men's); Basketball (Men's); Field Hockey; Cross Country (Men's); Football; Tennis (Men's); Track (Men's); Wrestling; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1928, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00137; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Baseball (Men's); Basketball (Women's); Basketball (Men's); Cross Country; Field Hockey; Tennis (Men's); Tennis (Women's); Wrestling; Football; Track (Men's); Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1929, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00138; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Baseball (Men's); Basketball (Women's); Basketball (Men's); Cross Country; Field Hockey; Football; Tennis (Women's); Tennis (Men's); Track (Men's); Wrestling; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1930, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00139; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Baseball (Men's); Baseball (Women's); Basketball (Men's); Basketball (Women's); Cross Country (Men's); Field Hockey; Football; Golf (Men's); Soccer (Men's); Tennis (Men's); Tennis (Women's); Track (Men's); Wrestling; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1931, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00140; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Archery (Women's); Baseball (Men's); Baseball (Women's); Basketball (Men's); Basketball (Women's); Cross Country (Men's); Field Hockey; Football; Golf (Men's); Lacrosse (Men's); Tennis (Men's); Tennis (Women's); Soccer (Men's); Track (Men's); Wrestling; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1932, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00141; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Archery (Women's); Baseball (Men's); Baseball (Women's); Basketball (Men's); Basketball (Women's); Cross Country (Men's); Field Hockey; Football; Golf (Men's); Outdoor Track (Men's); Soccer (Men's); Swimming (Women's); Tennis (Men's); Tennis (Women's); Wrestling; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1933, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00142; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Baseball (Men's); Baseball (Women's); Basketball (Men's); Basketball (Women's); Cross Country (Men's); Field Hockey; Football; Golf (Men's); Lacrosse (Men's); Outdoor Track (Men's); Soccer (Men's); Swimming (Women's); Tennis (Men's); Tennis (Women's); Wrestling; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1934, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00143; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Archery (Women's); Baseball (Men's); Basketball (Men's); Basketball (Women's); Cross Country (Men's); Field Hockey; Football; Golf (Men's); Indoor Track (Men's); Lacrosse (Men's); Outdoor Track (Men's); Outdoor Track (Women's); Soccer (Men's); Swimming (Women's); Tennis (Men's); Tennis (Women's); Wrestling; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1935, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00144; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Archery (Women's); Baseball (Men's); Basketball (Men's); Basketball (Women's); Cross Country (Men's); Field Hockey; Football; Golf (Men's); Indoor Track (Men's); Lacrosse (Men's); Outdoor Track (Men's); Soccer (Men's); Swimming (Women's); Tennis (Men's); Tennis (Women's); Wrestling; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1936, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00145; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Archery (Women's); Baseball (Men's); Basketball (Men's); Basketball (Women's); Cross Country (Men's); Field Hockey; Golf (Men's); Sport; Indoor Track (Men's); Lacrosse (Men's); Outdoor Track (Men's); Soccer (Men's); Swimming (Women's); Tennis (Men's); Tennis (Women's); Wrestling; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1937, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00146; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Archery (Women's); Baseball (Men's); Basketball (Men's); Basketball (Women's); Cross Country (Men's); Field Hockey; Golf (Men's); Indoor Track (Men's); Lacrosse (Men's); Outdoor Track (Men's); Soccer (Men's); Tennis (Men's); Wrestling; Football; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1938, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00147; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Baseball (Men's); Basketball (Men's); Basketball (Women's); Cross Country (Men's); Field Hockey; Golf (Men's); Indoor Track (Men's); Lacrosse (Men's); Outdoor Track (Men's); Soccer (Men's); Tennis (Men's); Wrestling; Football; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1939, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00148; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Baseball (Men's); Basketball (Men's); Basketball (Women's); Cross Country (Men's); Field Hockey; Football; Golf (Men's); Indoor Track (Men's); Lacrosse (Men's); Outdoor Track (Men's); Tennis (Men's); Soccer (Men's); Tennis (Women's); Wrestling; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1940, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00149; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Archery; Baseball (Men's); Basketball (Men's); Basketball (Women's); Cross Country (Men's); Fencing; Field Hockey; Football; Golf (Men's); Golf (Women's); Indoor Track (Men's); Lacrosse (Men's); Outdoor Track (Men's); Soccer (Men's); Tennis (Men's); Tennis (Women's); Wrestling; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1941, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00150; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Archery; Baseball (Men's); Basketball (Men's); Basketball (Women's); Cross Country (Men's); Field Hockey; Football; Golf (Women's); Indoor Track (Men's); Lacrosse (Men's); Outdoor Track (Men's); Soccer (Men's); Tennis (Men's); Wrestling; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1942, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00151; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Basketball (Men's); Basketball (Women's); Cross Country (Men's); Football; Golf (Women's); Indoor Track (Men's); Outdoor Track (Men's); Lacrosse (Men's); Soccer (Men's); Tennis (Men's); Wrestling; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1943, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00152; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Baseball (Men's); Basketball (Men's); Cross Country (Men's); Football; Indoor Track (Men's); Ice Hockey (Men's); Outdoor Track (Men's); Lacrosse (Men's); Soccer (Men's); Tennis (Men's); Wrestling; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1944, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00153; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Baseball (Men's); Basketball (Men's); Cross Country (Men's); Football; Indoor Track (Men's); Ice Hockey (Men's); Lacrosse (Men's); Outdoor Track (Men's); Wrestling; Soccer (Men's); Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1945, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00154; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Baseball (Men's); Basketball (Men's); Cross Country (Men's); Football; Indoor Track (Men's); Lacrosse (Men's); Outdoor Track (Men's); Soccer (Men's); Wrestling; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1946, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00155; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Baseball (Men's); Basketball (Men's); Cross Country (Men's); Football; Indoor Track (Men's); Lacrosse (Men's); Outdoor Track (Men's); Soccer (Men's); Swimming (Men's); Wrestling; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1947, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00156; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Baseball (Men's); Cross Country (Men's); Field Hockey; Basketball (Men's); Football; Golf (Men's); Ice Hockey (Men's); Indoor Track (Men's); Lacrosse (Men's); Outdoor Track (Men's); Soccer (Men's); Swimming (Men's); Wrestling; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1948, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00157; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Baseball (Men's); Basketball (Men's); Cross Country (Men's); Football; Golf (Men's); Ice Hockey (Men's); Indoor Track (Men's); Lacrosse (Men's); Outdoor Track (Men's); Skiing (Men's); Soccer (Men's); Softball; Swimming (Men's); Swimming (Women's); Tennis (Men's); Wrestling; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1949, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00158; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Baseball (Men's); Basketball (Men's); Basketball (Women's); Cross Country (Men's); Football; Field Hockey; Golf (Men's); Indoor Track (Men's); Lacrosse (Men's); Outdoor Track (Men's); Skiing (Men's); Soccer (Men's); Swimming (Men's); Swimming (Women's); Tennis (Men's); Wrestling; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1950, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00159; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Badminton (Women's); Baseball (Men's); Basketball; Basketball (Women's); Cross Country (Men's); Field Hockey; Football; Golf (Men's); Ice Hockey (Men's); Indoor Track (Men's); Lacrosse (Men's); Outdoor Track (Men's); Skiing (Men's); Soccer (Men's); Swimming (Men's); Swimming (Women's); Tennis (Men's); Tennis (Women's); Wrestling; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1951, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00160; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Archery (Women's); Badminton (Women's); Baseball (Men's); Basketball (Men's); Basketball (Women's); Cross Country (Men's); Field Hockey; Football; Golf (Men's); Ice Hockey (Men's); Indoor Track (Men's); Lacrosse (Men's); Outdoor Track (Men's); Skiing (Men's); Soccer (Men's); Squash (Men's); Tennis (Men's); Swimming (Men's); Tennis (Women's); Wrestling; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1952, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00161; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Archery (Women's); Baseball (Men's); Basketball (Men's); Basketball (Women's); Cross Country (Men's); Field Hockey; Football; Golf (Men's); Indoor Track (Men's); Ice Hockey (Men's); Outdoor Track (Men's); Skiing (Men's); Soccer (Men's); Lacrosse (Men's); Softball; Swimming (Men's); Swimming (Women's); Wrestling; Tennis (Men's); Tennis (Women's); Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1953, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00162; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Archery (Women's); Badminton (Women's); Baseball (Men's); Basketball (Men's); Basketball (Women's); Cross Country (Men's); Field Hockey; Football; Golf (Men's); Indoor Track (Men's); Ice Hockey (Men's); Lacrosse (Men's); Outdoor Track (Men's); Soccer (Men's); Softball; Swimming (Men's); Swimming (Women's); Tennis (Men's); Tennis (Women's); Wrestling; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1954, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00163; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1955, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00164; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Archery (Women's); Badminton (Women's); Baseball (Men's); Basketball (Men's); Basketball (Women's); Cross Country (Men's); Field Hockey; Football; Golf (Men's); Ice Hockey (Men's); Indoor Track (Men's); Outdoor Track (Men's); Lacrosse (Men's); Rifle Year Round; Skiing (Men's); Soccer (Men's); Swimming (Men's); Swimming (Women's); Tennis (Men's); Tennis (Women's); Wrestling; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1956, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00165; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Archery (Women's); Badminton (Women's); Baseball (Men's); Basketball (Men's); Basketball (Women's); Cross Country (Men's); Field Hockey; Football; Golf (Men's); Ice Hockey (Men's); Indoor Track (Men's); Lacrosse (Men's); Outdoor Track (Men's); Skiing (Men's); Soccer (Men's); Softball; Swimming (Men's); Swimming (Women's); Tennis (Men's); Tennis (Women's); Wrestling; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1957, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00166; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Badminton (Women's); Baseball (Men's); Basketball (Men's); Basketball (Women's); Cross Country (Men's); Field Hockey; Football; Golf; Ice Hockey (Men's); Indoor Track (Men's); Lacrosse (Men's); Outdoor Track (Men's); Skiing (Men's); Soccer (Men's); Softball; Swimming (Men's); Tennis (Men's); Tennis (Women's); Wrestling; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1958, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00167; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Archery (Women's); Badminton (Women's); Baseball; Basketball (Men's); Basketball (Women's); Cross Country (Men's); Field Hockey; Football; Golf (Men's); Ice Hockey (Men's); Indoor Track (Men's); Lacrosse (Men's); Outdoor Track (Men's); Soccer (Men's); Softball; Skiing (Men's); Swimming (Men's); Swimming (Women's); Tennis (Men's); Tennis (Women's); Wrestling; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1959, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00168; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Badminton (Women's); Baseball (Men's); Basketball (Men's); Basketball (Women's); Cross Country (Men's); Football; Golf (Men's); Ice Hockey (Men's); Indoor Track (Men's); Lacrosse (Men's); Outdoor Track (Men's); Rifle Team (Men's); Skiing (Men's); Soccer (Men's); Softball; Swimming (Men's); Swimming (Women's); Tennis (Men's); Tennis (Women's); Wrestling; Field Hockey; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1960, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00169; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Badminton (Women's); Baseball; Basketball (Men's); Basketball (Women's); Cross Country (Men's); Fencing (Women's); Field Hockey; Football; Golf (Men's); Indoor Track (Men's); Lacrosse (Men's); Outdoor Track (Men's); Skiing (Men's); Soccer (Men's); Softball; Swimming (Men's); Tennis (Men's); Tennis (Women's); Wrestling; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1961, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00170; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Badminton (Women's); Baseball; Basketball (Men's); Cross Country (Men's); Field Hockey; Football; Golf (Men's); Indoor Track (Men's); Lacrosse (Men's); Outdoor Track (Men's); Skiing (Men's); Soccer (Men's); Swimming (Men's); Tennis (Men's); Tennis (Women's); Wrestling; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1962, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00171; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Baseball (Men's); Basketball (Men's); Basketball (Women's); Cross Country (Men's); Field Hockey; Football; Golf (Men's); Indoor Track (Men's); Lacrosse (Men's); Outdoor Track (Men's); Skiing (Men's); Soccer (Men's); Softball; Swimming (Men's); Tennis (Men's); Wrestling; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1963, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00172; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Badminton (Women's); Baseball; Basketball (Men's); Basketball (Women's); Cross Country (Men's); Field Hockey; Football; Golf (Men's); Indoor Track (Men's); Lacrosse (Men's); Lacrosse (Women's); Outdoor Track (Men's); Skiing (Men's); Soccer (Men's); Swimming (Men's); Tennis (Men's); Wrestling; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1964, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00173; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Archery (Women's); Badminton (Women's); Baseball (Men's); Basketball (Men's); Basketball (Women's); Cross Country (Men's); Field Hockey; Football; Golf (Men's); Indoor Track (Men's); Lacrosse (Men's); Lacrosse (Women's); Outdoor Track (Men's); Sailing (Men's); Skiing (Men's); Soccer (Men's); Softball; Swimming (Men's); Tennis (Men's); Tennis (Women's); Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1965, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00174; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Badminton (Women's); Baseball (Men's); Basketball (Men's); Basketball (Women's); Cross Country (Men's); Field Hockey; Football; Golf (Men's); Indoor Track (Men's); Lacrosse (Men's); Outdoor Track (Men's); Sailing (Men's); Skiing (Men's); Soccer (Men's); Softball; Swimming (Men's); Tennis (Men's); Tennis (Women's); Wrestling; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1966, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00175; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Football; Soccer; Cross Country; Sailing; Basketball; Swimming; Indoor Track; Wrestling; Skiing; Baseball; Lacrosse; Tennis; Outdoor Track; Golf; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1967, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00176; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Football; Soccer; Cross Country; Sailing; Basketball; Swimming; Indoor Track; Wrestling; Skiing; Baseball; Golf; Lacrosse; Tennis; Outdoor Track; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1968, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00177; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Football; Soccer; Cross Country; Sailing; Basketball; Swimming; Indoor Track; Wrestling; Skiing; Baseball; Lacrosse; Golf; Tennis; Outdoor Track; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1969, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00178; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1970, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00179; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1971, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00180; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1972, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00181; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1973, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00182; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Football; Soccer (Men's); Sailing; Cross Country; Basketball; Skiing; Swimming; Indoor Track; Wrestling; Baseball; Tennis; Golf; Lacrosse; Outdoor Track; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1974, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00183; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Football; Soccer; Cross Country; Field Hockey; Tennis; Basketball (Men's); Skiing; Indoor Track; Wrestling; Basketball (Women's); Swimming; Baseball; Tennis; Golf; Lacrosse; Outdoor Track; Sailing (CoEd); Sailing (Women's); Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1975, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00184; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.
    Athletics; Football; Soccer; Sailing (Men's); Cross Country; Field Hockey; Tennis (Women's); Sailing (Women's); Basketball (Men's); Basketball (Women's); Squash (Men's); Squash (Women's); Swimming (Men's); Swimming (Women's); Indoor Track; Wrestling; Baseball; Golf; Lacrosse (Men's); Lacrosse (Women's); Tennis (Men's); Outdoor Track; Dept. of Phys. Ed./Athletics; Tufts University
  - Athletic Rosters of Tufts University for the year 1976, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00185; Kenny, Maura; Sauer, Anne; Crowley, Zachary E.